<?xml version="1.0"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0"><channel><title>Facebook Catalog Feed Updated: Tuesday 30th of March 2021 03:18:22 PM</title><link>https://www.nextleanacademy.com/</link><description>facebook products feed</description><item><g:id>33</g:id><g:title>Mastering Counselling</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/mastering-counselling</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 33-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>33-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ The A to Z of counseling is brought down to you through this amazing&nbsp;certificate course in Mastering Counselling. This comprehensive course is packed with lectures and guidance that will direct you towards mastery in counseling and all you have to do to enroll in this course is to just have a passion towards counseling. Not just general counseling, this course will also focus on areas such as career, marriage, family, group and individual counseling to further improve your scope of employment.

Starting off with an insight into the history of counseling and psychotherapy, this course will walk you through the process of counseling and the role, duties and responsibilities of a professional counselor. You will also gain the opportunity to model desirable counseling skills such as communication, empathy, understanding, and diplomacy.

The theoretical approaches to counseling, human growth, and development in counseling and the techniques used widely in counseling will be the few other topics that will touch upon in this course program. ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Counselling</g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>34</g:id><g:title>Corporate Finance</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/corporate-finance</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 34-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>34-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ Corporate finance is an aspect of finance that deals with funding, capital structure, investments, and many other financial aspects to maximize shareholder value. Corporate finance is a crucial part of an organisation and this Corporate Finance Course will teach you just why it is important. From the basic role of corporate finance to the more intermediate functions of it, this course will educate you on all that you need to know to seamlessly blend into the finance industry

Since one has to know the roles, duties, and responsibilities to perform them effectively, this course has dedicated a few modules that will look into it, after which you will be taught about capital budgeting and how to practically implement it within an organisation.

As part of the program, you will also be delving into the efficient market theory which is used widely to understand the behaviors of stocks within the corporate world. Real options, corporate financing, and valuation will then be given due attention. ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Financial Accounting</g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>35</g:id><g:title>Legal Secretary</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/legal-secretary</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 35-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>35-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ Whether you are a beginner or experienced secretary, the Legal Secretary course will empower you with the skills of working efficiently in a law office. The course provides great insight to legal terminology, an understanding of ethics in a law firm, displaying proper file management, learning to prepare legal documents and dealing with clients and their enquiries. It is a comprehensive and practical course that will keep you up to date with the legal requirements of working in an office, while undertaking administrative duties.

The course is extensive and will discuss key modules in-depth such as an introduction to legal English, basic legal principles, English courts, source of law and logical reasoning. Each topic will be explored fully to ensure learners gain a complete understanding of the subject matter.

There are a number of duties of a legal secretary that has to be carried out. The Legal Secretary course will help learners demonstrate their understanding of law, legal procedures, secretarial skills and computer literacy. It is a fantastic course that will give you the opportunity to take you a step closer to becoming a qualified legal secretary. This will open the door to exciting opportunities and future career prospects. ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Legal Secretary</g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>36</g:id><g:title>Business Analysis</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/business-analysis</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 36-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>36-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ Identifying the emerging business needs and solving it tactfully determines the success of an organisation, which is why the importance of business analysis and such professionals have increased drastically in the modern world. The business analysis industry is a great platform for individuals who are creative enough to identify and solve problems and to direct the business towards prosperity.

If you too have dreamt of a career in business analysis, this Business Analysis course could be the qualification that gets you into the industry. This course with its interesting training materials will help you put knowledge into practice and turn business analysis into an art that you cannot get enough of.

From the role of business analysis to the techniques and methods used to measure business performance, this course has beautifully explored all corners of business analysis, along with an insight into the fundamentals such as the duties and responsibilities of a business analyst. ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Business Analysis</g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>37</g:id><g:title>Gardening and Landscaping</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/gardening-and-landscaping</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 37-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>37-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ Owning a well-maintained garden could add a little bit of quality, peace, and serenity to life that is genuinely unexplainable. With urbanization, the need for a bit of greenery in the surrounding has only increased, with more and more people establishing gardens around their houses or businesses. As a result, the gardening and landscaping industry has seen some significant growth and the demand for professional gardeners and landscapers has also increased

If you too wish to put your passion towards gardening and landscaping into a career, then this course in&nbsp;Gardening and Landscaping&nbsp;might be the right place to get started. Not just for aspiring individuals, people who would like to learn about gardening and landscaping to maintain and beautify his/her gardens might also greatly benefit from this program.

The latest trends in landscaping and gardening, the challenging conditions of maintaining trees and shrubs, how to plant trees and shrubs, how to care for trees and shrubs during winter, summer and spring and how restore a landscape back to health will all be taught abundantly through this course program. ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Landscaping and Gardening</g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>41</g:id><g:title>Mastering Public Speaking</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/mastering-public-speaking</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 41-image.jpeg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>41-image.jpeg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ Not everyone likes the idea of public speaking. In fact, the very idea can make people feel nervous. However, there may be instances when you have to speak publicly either in your career or even as a student. Public speaking, once you master it, can be immensely interesting and fun. If you want to learn the art of public speaking, follow this course in Mastering Public Speaking&nbsp;and be armed with the tools and techniques to become an effective public speaker. &nbsp;&nbsp;

The course covers key modules such as research and organise your speech, how to speak and listen well, outlining your speech and style and methods of persuasion. Each topic will be discussed extensively, ensuring learners gain a complete understanding of the subject matter.

Mastering Public Speaking Course will focus on how to not just speak effectively but also how to keep your audience engaged from start to finish. There is no point in just learning to speak in public, you need to understand your audience and adjust your style of speaking in order to cater to them. Becoming an effective public speaker will get you recognised by your employer and create that wow factor because they find you highly impressive. ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Other Courses</g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>42</g:id><g:title>Accounting Essentials</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/accounting-essentials</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 42-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>42-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ Would you like to learn the fundamentals of accounting and pursue a career in the industry? The Accounting Essentials course is the perfect training for you to make a mark in the field and land your dream job role. It is a practical course that provides in-depth knowledge and gives you a complete understanding of the essentials of accounting. &nbsp;

Accounting Essentials course will introduce learners to a number of key topics such as basics of financial statements, income statements, balance sheets, and cash flow statements. Each module is fully explored ensuring learners gain a comprehensive understanding of the subject matter discussed. What is great about this course is that you can come to it without prior knowledge of accounting, and simply because you want to learn and enhance your understanding, or because you are contemplating a career change. &nbsp;

The Accounting Essentials course will make you an efficient worker in the accounting industry, and someone who has the skill to excel in a working environment. This course is also perfect for students who want to progress in their academic education and have a career in this field. ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Financial Accounting</g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>43</g:id><g:title>Public Speaking Essential Training</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/public-speaking-essential-training</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 43-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>43-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ The idea of public speaking can make people experience stress and nerves. However, there may be instances when you have to speak publicly either in your career or at a special occasion. Additionally, there are students who need to present their work in front of a class. Public speaking is an art and once mastered, you will learn to love it. This Public Speaking Essential Training Course will equip you with the tools and techniques to become an effective public speaker.&nbsp;&nbsp;

The course covers key modules such as how to overcome the fear of public speaking, how to prepare your speech and how to deliver your speech effecitvely. Each topic will be discussed extensively, ensuring learners gain a complete understanding of the subject matter.

The Public Speaking Essential Training Course will focus on how to prepare your speech and deliver it effectively to an audience. It is also important that you know your audience before preparing a speech. Learn to adjust your style accordingly to ensure they remain engaged throughout the speech. Becoming an effective public speaker will get you recognised by your employer and create that wow factor because they find your skillset highly impressive. ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Other Courses</g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>44</g:id><g:title>Accounting for Business</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/accounting-for-business</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 44-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>44-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ If you want to take your career in accounting to the next level, the Accounting for Business course ticks all the right boxes. It is the perfect course to enjoy a long-standing career in the accounting industry. This course is practical and gives you an in-depth knowledge of the core practices and principles involved in accounting basics. The qualification will make you a marketable candidate and give you a competitive edge in the industry.

Accounting is central to any enterprise and when it is given its significant due, you can ensure the overall success of a company. This course will help you advance in your knowledge of accounting for business. If you aspire to setup your own business, gaining the fundamentals of accounting through this course will give you the foundation to succeed.

The Accounting for Business course will make you an efficient worker in the accounting industry, and someone who has the skill to excel in their workplace. Students who are studying this course will gain a plethora of opportunities to progress in their academic education and have a career in this field. ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Financial Accounting</g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>45</g:id><g:title>Classroom Management</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/classroom-management</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 45-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>45-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ Do you enjoy teaching? Would you like to improve your classroom management skills? The course Classroom Management Training is the perfect fit for you to boost your teaching career. Additionally, parents will also find this course beneficial as it focuses on the education of young people. You will learn the latest classroom management strategies, how to maintain discipline in an educational setting and how to create a motivating environment that compels students to learn.

The course will explore key modules and discuss them at length, such as basics of classroom management, communication in the modern classroom, theories of classroom management and motivation in the classroom. Learners will gain a complete understanding of the subject matter.

The Classroom Management Course&nbsp;is ideal for teachers in primary school right until advanced education. The course will give you the confidence to apply your management skills in the classroom and reap successful outcomes. The course contains a wealth of information and offers insight into the effectiveness of classroom management skills. The qualification will also enable you to progress in your career in the educational field. &nbsp; ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Educational Training</g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>47</g:id><g:title>Fundamentals of Human Molecular Genetics</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/fundamentals-of-human-molecular-genetics</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 47-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>47-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ The Fundamentals of Human Molecular Genetics Course is an introduction to understand the role of human genome in health and disease. The course will focus on the underlying molecular pathology that will eventually help us understand the cause of diseases and medical conditions that we may not currently comprehend. It is an extensive course packed with a wealth of information that introduced key concepts of human traits, chromosomes and pedigree analysis.

The course will feature key modules such as discovering human genetics, transmission of mendelian genetics, definition of comparative genomics, exploring DNA technology and transgenic organisms. Each module will be extensively discussed to ensure learners gain a complete understanding of the subject matter.

The Fundamentals of Human Molecular Genetics Course, You will become a marketable candidate with the potential to impress leading organisations.&nbsp; Be a competitive force across multiple sectors across a broad spectrum and give your career the kick-start you&rsquo;ve always wanted. ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Biology &amp; Chemistry</g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>48</g:id><g:title>Human Biology</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/human-biology</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 48-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>48-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ Are you interested in learning about human biology? Maybe science piques your interest and fascinates you. If you would like to aim for a career in biology, the Human Biology Course&nbsp;is the perfect course for you. Biology is life of science that helps us understand all living things and how they function. Learn to analyse the fundamental biological principles in relation to the human biology.

The course covers a range of key modules such the fundamentals of human biology, the respiratory system, human circulatory system, and guide to blood vessels, the muscular system and understanding the digestive system. Each module will be explored comprehensively to ensure learners gain a complete understanding of the subject matter.

The Human Biology Course is practical as it is comprehensive and will teach you everything you need to know about the endocrine system, learning about disease and disorders and the skeletal system. A specialised certification such as this will give your resume a boost, and improve career prospects across a broad spectrum. ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Biology &amp; Chemistry</g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>50</g:id><g:title>Advanced Online Marketing</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/advanced-online-marketing</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 50-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>50-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ The digital world is booming, and everything and everyone seems to have gone digital. Whether you are looking to make a career change, you already work in online marketing or you aspire to, the Advanced Online Marketing will be highly beneficial for you to move up the career ladder. The course will teach you how to integrate online marketing with the overall marketing strategy in the organisation. &nbsp;You will be fully equipped with the relevant skills and expertise to plan digital marketing campaigns on social media networks, engage in search marketing and email affiliates. If you run your own marketing company, this course will be advantageous to gain insight into how the concept of online marketing works, and how it can bring you success in the industry.

The course will cover key modules such as an understanding of online marketing, digital marketing campaigns, essentials of Google analytics, social media networks, SEO methodologies and SEO marketing tips. Each topic is discussed extensively to ensure learners gain a complete understanding of the subject matter.

The Advanced Online Marketing&nbsp;will enhance your digital capabilities and will give you a broad understanding of how to excel within this industry. Once qualified, there will be exciting opportunities for you to land the job you deserve.&nbsp; ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Digital Marketing </g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>51</g:id><g:title>Animal Psychology</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/animal-psychology</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 51-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>51-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ Sometimes pets too can become unhappy. When that happens, what can you do? Do you know how to read the signs, understand troubled behaviour or identify aggression and anxiety? Animal Psychology course offers an overview of how to have a complete and clear understanding of pet psychology. It is a comprehensive course that will help you to build a trusting relationship with your pet so that you will be able to focus more effectively when it comes to understanding its psychology and recognising important behavioural patterns. Learn how to ensure your pet remains happy and healthy, at all times. If you&rsquo;ve aspired to work in animal psychology, this course has all what it takes to achieve your career goals. &nbsp;&nbsp;

The course will cover key topics such as normal behaviour of dogs, behaviour of junior and senior dogs, how to calm aggression, fear and anxiety, and understanding dogs antics. Each module will be explored in-depth, ensuring learners gain a firm understanding of what it takes to enhance their knowledge in animal psychology.

The&nbsp;Animal Psychology Course will offer insight on why some pets are afraid, anxious or aggressive. Often, this is not normal behavioural and through the course you will learn to identify what triggers this type of behaviour in animals. The course will educate you on why pets behave in a certain way, the reasoning behind it, and how to resolve it with love, kindness and patience. ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Animal Psychology</g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>52</g:id><g:title>Marketing for Business</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/marketing-for-business</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 52-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>52-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ There are different types of methods to market a product and service, but which methods are the most effective? If you want to get ahead in your business and find the appropriate marketing strategies and tools, the Marketing for Business is the right course for you. The course is practical and covers the fundamentals of marketing and the opportunity to gain the relevant expertise in the industry. Having a specialist qualification on your CV will make you a recognised candidate enabling you to land the job you&rsquo;ve always wanted. &nbsp;

The course covers a range of key modules such as how to develop your marketing plan, low cost marketing skills, developing your brand identity and understanding the function of your website. Each module will be extensively discussed to ensure learners gain a complete understanding of the subject matter.

The Marketing for Business will help you develop an understanding of sales strategies, public relations and advertising techniques and the impact of social media marketing. This course is comprehensive, and you will be equipped with the necessary skills and knowledge to bring out the best in your website, and give your business a solid boost. ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Digital Marketing </g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>53</g:id><g:title>Advanced Management Skills</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/advanced-management-skills</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 53-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>53-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ Would you like to gain basic management skills? Maybe you aspire to take on a managerial role someday. If you want to learn the fundamentals of management, the Advanced Management Skills course is the perfect course for you. The course will demonstrate how you can motivate, influence and inspire teams and people working for you. You will learn to exercise your leadership and management skills in order to build successful teams that produce high performance within an organisation.

The course covers a range of key modules such as the fundamentals of advanced management skills, basic management skills, essential management skills and concepts of management paradigms. Each module will be heavily discussed to ensure learners gain a complete understanding of the subject matter.

The Advanced Management Skills course will help you develop leadership traits and improve your management of teams. This course is practical as it is comprehensive, and you will be equipped with the relevant skills and expertise to bring out the best in others, retain employees and empower talent. ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Business Administration</g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>55</g:id><g:title>Home Improvement - DYI</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/home-improvement-dyi</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 55-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>55-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ Not everyone has the time or skill to do their own home decoration and interior designing. Often, qualified and professional providers are sought for their services. If this is an area that interests you, why not get certified in this regard. The Diploma in Home Improvement DIY is the perfect course to help you become established in your own home improvement or interior design business.

The course covers a range of key modules such as getting started, decorating, outdoor projects and dealing with pests. Each module will be explored comprehensively to ensure learners gain a complete understanding of the subject matter.

The Home Improvement DIY course will teach you various decorating techniques in order to become a pro at home improvement. Learn about security systems and how to install them in your home, and your client&rsquo;s home. Gaining this certification will give potential and new clients the confidence to take on your services. A specialised certification such as this will give your resume a boost, and improve career prospects. ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Interior Decorating</g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>57</g:id><g:title>Diabetes Awareness</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/diabetes-awareness</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 57-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>57-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ Diabetes is a common medical condition and millions of people get affected yearly. If you want to learn more about this condition and gain a complete understanding of how the disease impacts people, the Diabetes Awareness Course is an ideal course. It is designed for healthcare professionals who want to raise awareness of the disease and provide better care for diabetes patients.

The course will cover key modules such as what is diabetes, types of diabetes, symptoms, maintain a healthy life and medication. Each topic is discussed extensively to ensure learners gain a complete understanding of the subject matter.

The Diabetes Awareness Course is effective to support the development of healthcare professionals who want to enhance their knowledge of diabetes and raise awareness of the condition. The course will fully equip you to have a strong understanding of the condition and provide support to diabetic individuals accordingly. You will become familiar with short and long-term risks, treatment methods available and how to assist in their day to day lives. ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Health Care</g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>58</g:id><g:title>Nannying and Childcare Training</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/nannying-and-childcare-training</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 58-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>58-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ If you want to have a career in childcare, here&rsquo;s a great opportunity to gain a recognised certification. Nannying and Childcare coursehas been designed to equip you with the fundamental skills and knowledge of what it takes to be a caregiver and the responsibilities this role entails. This provides an excellent training for individuals who want to work with children and foster their growth and development in a healthy and balanced manner.&nbsp;&nbsp;

The course will explore key modules that will focus on essentials for nannies, establishing a routine, health and safety and working with parents. Each topic will be extensively discussed to ensure the learner gains a complete understanding of the subject matter.&nbsp;

Nannying and Childcare Training will provide you with an opportunity to progress in your career in the childcare industry. The course is also suitable for students who want to acquire the relevant skills and understanding of childcare, and how to take on such an in-depth role. ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Childcare Training </g:google_product_category></item><item><g:id>59</g:id><g:title>Office Administration &amp; Reception</g:title><g:link>http://localnla/course/office-administration-reception</g:link><g:image_link><![CDATA[ 59-image.jpg ]]></g:image_link><additional_image_link>59-image.jpg</additional_image_link><g:description><![CDATA[ Gain knowledge of office administration and receptionist duties with the Office Administration &amp; Reception Course. What&rsquo;s so great about this course is that once qualified you have a range of job options you can choose to enter, whether it is as an administrative assistant, secretary or HR assistant. The course offers insight on the role and tasks pertaining to office administration. Whether you are new to this field or employed and want to learn new skills, getting qualified will make you a marketable candidate with a competitive edge across multiple industries.

Office Administrators are responsible for various duties and this course covers key modules such as developing customer service skills, developing business writing, tips for speed reading and handling confidential documents. All topics will be extensively discussed with learners gaining a complete understanding of the subject matter.

The Office Administration &amp; Reception course will teach learners office administration and reception matters and how to progress in your career in this regard. The course will focus on basic skills and competencies of getting the job done right. It is also useful for students who want to study further in this field. ]]></g:description><g:price>49.00 GBP</g:price><g:availability>in stock</g:availability><g:condition><![CDATA[ New ]]></g:condition><g:brand><![CDATA[ Next Learn Academy ]]></g:brand><g:product_type><![CDATA[ CPD ]]></g:product_type><g:google_product_category>Office Admin Assistants</g:google_product_category></item></channel></rss>